# HASSAN KHABIBULLAEV

# Frontend Developer & Business Systems Analyst

+998 99 977 00 70 · Tashkent, Uzbekistan · <u>khassanboi@gmail.com</u> <u>khassanboi.com · linkedin.com/in/khassanboi · github.com/khassanboi</u>

As a Frontend Developer, I excel in creating engaging user experiences with HTML, CSS (including Bootstrap and SASS/SCSS), and JavaScript (including ReactJS). In the realm of Business Systems Analysis, I specialize in streamlining operations and driving efficiency through integrated systems management.

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- HTML (Semantic Markup, JSX) & CSS (Bootstrap, Adaptive/Responsive, BEM, SASS/SCSS):
- **JavaScript** (TypeScript, ReactJS, Redux, React Hooks, entry-level NodeJS/Express)
- Integrated Systems Management (Workflow Automation: Zapier, Make.com, custom scripting; Data Management and Analysis: AirTable, Salesforce, PowerTools)
- **Ops Management & Business Systems Analysis** (project and quality management, strategic planning, resource allocation, process improvement, performance monitoring, presentation)

# WORK EXPERIENCE

**Global Friends** - Tashkent, Uzbekistan

August 2021 - present

#### **Business Systems Analyst and Operations Manager**

- Was responsible for operations improvement with automations, portal and landing page development, technical support, and student enrollment coordination.
- Reduced processing time of document generation such as invoices and generic letters from 5
  minutes to 1 second with a single click, achieving a 300-fold boost in efficiency.
- Improved data management efficiency significantly by implementing an integrated student portal which served as a centralized platform for managing student information.
- Boosted marketing strategies by developing customized landing pages for various services offered by the company. They are present in my web portfolio.
- Began as Operations Assistant and advanced to the current position in January 2022.

**EPAM Systems** - Tashkent, Uzbekistan

May 2021 - January 2022

#### **Frontend Developer**

- Designed and developed HTML/CSS layouts to support web application and component development projects, focusing on both functionality and UI optimization.
- Helped backend developers with frontend tasks for UI integration and performance improvement, as well as with adapting to new updates.
- Revamped online library and documentation portal web pages, enhancing readability and accessibility for improved UX and navigation efficiency.
- Completed a 3-months long internship program initially and transitioned to this position.

# **EDUCATION**

# Westminster International University in Tashkent - Tashkent, Uzbekistan

May 2023

Bachelors of Science with Honors - Business Information Systems

Achieved a GPA of 80% based on UK grading system with 70% denoting a distinctive mark

Earned a First-Class Honors Diploma

# Academic Lyceum of TashSUULL - Tashkent, Uzbekistan

May 2019

Secondary Education - Foreign Philology

 $Achieved\ a\ GPA\ of\ 5\ based\ on\ Uzbekistan\ grading\ system\ with\ 5\ denoting\ a\ maximum\ mark$ 

Earned a First-Class Honors Diploma

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

# Westminster International University in Tashkent

October 2020 - April 2023

- Served as a Course Representative for my program and level.
- Facilitated the "70+ BIS" club to assist fellow students.
- Acted as a Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador to the university.

# **LANGUAGES**

**Uzbek** - Native

**English** - Proficient (IELTS 8.0)

Russian - Proficient

French - Intermediate